const daySevenQuestions = [
  {
    question:
      "How many classes do we have when we classify Hadith according to the number of reporters involved in each stage of Sanad?",
    options: ["4 Classes", "2 Classes", "6 Classes", "5 Classes", "3 Classes"],
    correctOption: 0,
  },
  {
    question:
      "When classifying Hadith according to the accepted and rejected (this is done according to reliability and memory of the reporters) we have how many classes?",
    options: ["4 Classes", "2 Classes", "6 Classes", "5 Classes", "3 Classes"],
    correctOption: 4,
  },
  {
    question: "What a reporter of Hadith adds to the Hadith is called…?",
    options: ["Al Mudallas", "As Shadh", "Al Mudraj", "Al Mawdu’", "Al Munkar"],
    correctOption: 2,
  },
  {
    question:
      "… means a Hadith which is weak due to the uncertainty caused by concealed defects made by the reporter of that Hadith.",
    options: ["Al Mudallas", "As Shadh", "Al Mudraj", "Al Mawdu’", "Al Munkar"],
    correctOption: 0,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the name of the Hadith that the reporter at the end of transmitters after ‘Successor’ was omitted?",
    options: ["Al Mursal", "Al Mawdu’", "Al Mudraj", "Al Munkar", "Al Gareeb"],
    correctOption: 0,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the name of the Hadith that only one single reporter is found narrating it some stage of Isnad?",
    options: [
      "Al Hadith ‘Aziz",
      "Al Mawdu’",
      "Al Mudraj",
      "Al Munkar",
      "Al Gareeb",
    ],
    correctOption: 4,
  },
  {
    question:
      "A Hadith narrated from Prophet is Marfu (Elevated) while a Hadith narrated from the Companion is …?",
    options: [
      "Al Hadith ‘Aziz",
      "Al Mawquf",
      "Al Mudraj",
      "Al Munqati’",
      "Al Maqtu’",
    ],
    correctOption: 1,
  },

  {
    question: "Four classifications of accepted hadiths are…, …, … and …",
    options: [
      "Sahih, Hassan, Gareeb and Maqlub",
      "Sahih, Hassan, Gareeb and Musalsal",
      "Sahih, Hassan, Gareeb and Shadh",
      "Sahih, Hassan, Mahfuz and Shadh",
      "Sahih lithatih, Sahih ligayrih, Hassan lithatih and Hassan ligayrih",
    ],
    correctOption: 4,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Two generally accepted reasons for rejecting a Hadith are … and …",
    options: [
      "Chain and Content",
      "Lie and Fabrication",
      "Interruption in the chain of transmission and Defects",
      "Period and Contradiction",
      "Obscure and Time",
    ],
    correctOption: 2,
  },
  {
    question:
      "When two connected people narrate a Hadith from each other, the narration is called…?",
    options: [
      "Al Mudabbaj",
      "Riwayatul aqran",
      "Al Musalsal",
      "Al Ma’ruf",
      "Al Mahfuz",
    ],
    correctOption: 0,
  },
  {
    question:
      "………………………is a Hadith that in each stage of Isnad only two reporters are found narrating it.",
    options: [
      "Al Hadith ‘Aziz",
      "Al Mawdu’",
      "Al Mudraj",
      "Al Munkar",
      "Al Gareeb",
    ],
    correctOption: 0,
  },
  {
    question:
      "………………………………………is a Hadith that is narrated by a liar or the content of the Hadith is against Islamic rules.",
    options: [
      "Al Mursal",
      "Al Maodu’",
      "Al Mudraj",
      "Al Munqati’",
      "Al Gareeb",
    ],
    correctOption: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Science of Hadith is classified in to two, what are they?",
    options: [
      "Sahih and Da’eef",
      "Isnad and Matn",
      "Ilm lhadith Riwayah and Ilm lhadith Dirayah",
      "Ilm Rijal and Ilm Riwayah",
      "Maqbul and Mardud",
    ],
    correctOption: 2,
  },
  {
    question:
      "………………………is a Hadith that has uninterrupted Isnad narrated by reliable traditionalists with high retentive memory from another traditionalist of the same status, and void of irregularity and defects.",
    options: [
      "Hadith Hassan",
      "Hadith Sahih",
      "Hadith Gareeb",
      "Hadith Da’eef",
      "Hadith Mashur",
    ],
    correctOption: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "When only one of the two connected people narrates Hadith from his partner and his partner did not narrate any from him, the narration is called…?",
    options: [
      "Al Mudabbaj",
      "Riwayatul aqran",
      "Al Musalsal",
      "Al Ma’ruf",
      "Al Mahfuz",
    ],
    correctOption: 1,
  },
];
export default daySevenQuestions;
